 [
    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does DM (Eastern Kingdom) refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Deadmines", "Deadmines"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SFK refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Shadowfang Keep"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does STK refer to?",
      "Answers": [
        "The Stormwind Stockade",
        "Stormwind Stockade",
        "The Stockade",
        "Stockade"
      ],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does GR refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Gnomeregan"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SM refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Scarlet Monastery", "Scarlet Monastery"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Uld refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Uldaman"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does ST refer to?",
      "Answers": [
        "The Temple of Atal'Hakkar",
        "Temple of Atal'Hakkar",
        "Sunken Temple"
      ],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does BRD refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Blackrock Depths", "Blackrock Depths"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does LBRS refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Lower Blackrock Spire"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does UBRS refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Upper Blackrock Spire"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does BRS refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Blackrock Spire"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Strat refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Stratholme"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Scholo refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Scholomance", "Scholomance"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does ZG refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Zul'Gurub"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does MC refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Molten Core", "Molten Core"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does BWL refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Blackwing Lair", "Blackwing Lair"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Naxx refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Naxxramas"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does KZ refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Karazhan"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does ZA refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Zul'Aman"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does MgT refer to?",
      "Answers": [
        "The Magisters' Terrace",
        "Magisters' Terrace",
        "The Magisters Terrace",
        "Magisters Terrace"
      ],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SWP refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Sunwell Plateau", "Sunwell Plateau"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does RFC refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Ragefire Chasm"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does WC refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Wailing Caverns", "Wailing Caverns"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does BFD refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Blackfathom Deeps", "Blackfathom Deeps"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does RFK refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Razorfen Kraul"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does RFD refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Razorfen Downs"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does ZF refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Zul'Farrak"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Mara refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Maraudon"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does DM (Kalimdor) refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Dire Maul"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Ony refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Onyxia's Lair", "Onyxia"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does AQ20 refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Ruins of Ahn'Qiraj", "Ruins of Ahn'Qiraj"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does AQ40 refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Temple of Ahn'Qiraj", "Temple of Ahn'Qiraj"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does CoT: OHF refer to?",
      "Answers": [
        "Old Hillsbrad Foothills",
        "Caverns of Time: Old Hillsbrad Foothills",
        "Escape from Durnholde Keep"
      ],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does CoT: BM refer to?",
      "Answers": [
        "Black Morass",
        "Caverns of Time: Black Morass",
        "Opening the Dark Portal"
      ],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does MH refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Hyjal Summit", "Battle to Mount Hyjal", "Mount Hyjal"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does CoT: Strat refer to?",
      "Answers": [
        "Old Stratholme",
        "Caverns of Time: Old Stratholme",
        "Culling of Stratholme"
      ],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What zone does HFC refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Hellfire Citadel"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does HFR refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Hellfire Ramparts", "Hellfire Ramparts", "Ramparts"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does BF refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Blood Furnace", "Blood Furnace"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SP refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Slave Pens", "Slave Pens"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does UB refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Underbog", "Underbog"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does MT refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Mana Tombs", "Mana Tombs"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does AC refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Auchenai Crypts", "Auchenai Crypts"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Seth refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Sethekk Halls", "Sethekk Halls"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SV refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Steamvault", "Steamvault", "Steam Vaults"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SL refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Shadow Labyrinth", "Shadow Labyrinth", "Shadow Lab"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Mech refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Mechanar", "Mechanar"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Bot refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Botanica", "Botanica"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Arc refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Arcatraz", "Arcatraz"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SH refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Shattered Halls", "Shattered Halls"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Gruul refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Gruul's Lair", "Gruul the Dragonkiller"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Mag refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Magtheridon's Lair", "Magtheridon"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does SSC refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Serpentshrine Cavern"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does TK refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Eye", "Tempest Keep"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does BT refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Black Temple", "Black Temple"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does UK refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Utgarde Keep"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Nex refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Nexus", "Nexus"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does AN refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Azjol-Nerub", "Nerub"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does DTK refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Drak'Tharon Keep"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does HoS refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Halls of Stone", "Halls of Stone"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does UP refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Utgarde Pinnacle"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Ocu refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Oculus", "Oculus"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does HoL refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Halls of Lightning", "Halls of Lightning"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does EoE refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Eye of Eternity", "Eye of Eternity"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does ICC refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Icecrown Citadel", "Icecrown Citadel"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does CoA refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Chamber of Aspects", "Chamber of Aspects"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does Gun refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Gun'Drak", "Gundrak"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does VH refer to?",
      "Answers": ["The Violet Hold", "Violet Hold"],
      "Category": 3,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does AB refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Arathi Basin"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does AV refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Alterac Valley"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does EotS refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Eye of the Storm"],
      "Category": 2,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What instance does WSG refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Warsong Gulch"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    },

    {
      "Question": "Acronym: What zone does CoT refer to?",
      "Answers": ["Caverns of Time"],
      "Category": 1,
      "Points": 5,
      "Hints": ""
    }
  ]
